ASHLEY MILLER

1003 Tennessee Street, Kannapolis, NC 28083

Ph: (828) 553-5241

acmiller615@gmail.com

Summary

Goal-oriented Community Association Manager dedicated to high levels of customer satisfaction and meeting aggressive business goals. Organized and personable with specialized knowledge in leadership and customer service.

Skills

- Excel
- Administration and Management
- Outlook
- Customer and Personal Service
- Publisher
- Critical Thinking
- Speaking
- Microsoft Word

Experience

Community Association Manager

Cedar Management Group - Charlotte, NC

Jan 2014-Jun 2016

- Manage 19 communities.
- Manage all aspects of community including violations, maintenance, accounting, review AR monthly and proceed with deliquent accounts, ensure all activities and practices remain legal.
- Meet with Boards on a regular basis and prepare location, information and documents for Annual and Board meetings, conduct voting and assure meeting remains constructive.

Office Support

Aug 2013-Jan 2014

Ammons Superior Plumbing - Indian Trail, NC

 Answer phones, schedule jobs and dispatch to technicians, bill customers, track payments, backflow scheduling and ordering of parts, track time of technicians and jobs, assist in all clerical needs.

Office Manager

Mar 2012-Jan 2013

Perfect Balance - Brevard, NC

 Answer phones, schedule appointments, check patients in/out, collect payments, assist with billing/insurance, track inventory, check pool chemicals daily, customer emails, marketing, work closely with owners to ensure business was growing and running smoothly.

Office Manager

Sep 2001-Mar 2012

Millers Auto Parts - Rosman, NC

- Accounts payable, accounts receivable, balance check book, set up all customer accounts, figure monthly sales tax, set up all vendor accounts.
- Enter all information into QuickBooks; work one-on-one with accountant to

help business run efficiently, payroll and payroll liabilities.

Education

Real Estate Broker Rowan-Cabarrus Business and Technology Center - Concord, NC	Sep 2016
Bachelor of Arts: Social Science Ashford University - Clinton , IA	Oct 2011
Certification in QuickBooks Blue Ridge Community College - Brevard, NC	<i>Apr 2003</i>

References

available upon request